Guide to the Cornell Campus Club records, 1900-2015.
Cornell Campus Club records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Campus Club records, 1900-2015.
11-8-390
Cornell Campus Club.
2.3 cubic ft.
Organizational records, printed material, and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Secretary's and treasurer's reports, minutes of the executive board and various committees and annual meetings, constitutions, lists of officers, newsletters and brochures, samples of printed forms, reports of activity groups, social reports, newcomers' items, history of the Campus Club, and miscellaneous items.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Cornell women's organization, formed in 1900 to "welcome newcomers to the campus and to promote friendship among the women at Cornell."
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Secretary's and treasurer's reports, minutes of the executive board and various committees and annual meetings, constitutions, lists of officers, newsletters and brochures, samples of printed forms, reports of activity groups (1936-1941), social reports, newcomers' items (1949-1953), history of the Campus Club, and miscellaneous items. Includes correspondence of Mary H. Donlon, Emily Day, and Helen A. Newman. Also includes a VHS videotape made by the Quilting Group of the Campus Club in 1995 of the presentation of a quilt to Frank and Rosa Rhodes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Campus Club.
Subjects:
Women -- New York (State) -- Ithaca -- Societies and clubs.; Women -- Societies and clubs
Places:
New York (State) -- Ithaca
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
This collection includes collection #11-8-99.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Cornell Campus Club Annual Reports
Series II. Assorted Campus Club Records
CONTAINER LIST
- Cornell Campus Club Annual Reports, Expression
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cornell Campus Club Annual Report, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Assorted Campus Club Records, 1900-2014
  - Campus Club Records, 1900-1909 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Campus Club Miscellaneous Records, 1900-1910 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1901-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Officers of the Campus Club, 1902-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campus Club Records, 1910-1919 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campus Club Records, 1920-1929 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Campus Club Records Printing Samples, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitutions & By-laws, 1929, 1948, 1954, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campus Club History, 1929-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1930-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1930-1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Activity Groups, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Activity Groups, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Campus Club Scrapbook, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Old Timers of Campus Club, 1949-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Service Groups, 1956-1967-08 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Activity Group- International Committee, 1957-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Meeting Reports & Miscellaneous, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1960-10-1969-12 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Antiques Study Group, 1963-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - International Hospitality Committee, 1963-2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Activity Group - Sage Auxiliary, 1967-01 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Activity Group - Professional Skills Roster, 1967-05-1968-02 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1969-06-1976-06 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Activity Groups, 1970-01-1970-03 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Donations Over the Years, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Nelli Carson Tree Dedication, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1976-06-1980-05 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Campus Club Records, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1980-05-1986-11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1986-05-1990-05 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Wanderer's File, 1987-1991-06 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1990-05-1994-09 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Activity Groups - General, 1995-06-1995-07 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1995-06-1999-03 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Invitations, 2000-12-2014-05 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Centennial Photos, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Centennial Materials, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cornell Campus Club Archives Information, 2001-09-2001-10 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cornell Campus Club Assorted Files, 2002-02-2003-02 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Secretary's Books, 1948-1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Secretary's Books, 1953-1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Documents, 1959-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 75th Anniversary Guest Book, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Campus Club Executive Board Notebook, 1980-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Campus Club Choral Group, 1931-1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Quilt, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Campus Club Chorus Music Library Inventory, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Campus Club Secretary Books, 1901-1941, 1902-1912, 1912-1920, 1920-1929 (Box 3)
  - Cornell Campus Club Secretary Books, 1929-1938, 1938-1948, 1941-1969 (Box 3)